[
        {
                "question": "Which one of these is not a Map in PUBG?",
                "option": ["Vikendi", "Sanhok", "Erangel", "Jhumri Telaiya"],
                "answer": "Jhumri Telaiya"
        },
        {
                "question": "A player is awarded as which of these ranks in PUBG?",
                "option": ["Diamond", "Silver", "Ace", "All of these"],
                "answer": "All of these"
        },
        {
                "question": "Which among these games, do similar to PUBG?",
                "option": ["Call Of Duty", "Subway Surfers", "Candy Crush Saga", "Need For Speed"],
                "answer": "Call Of Duty"
        },
        {
                "question": "This game is developed by which of the following company?",
                "option": ["Activision", "Ubisoft", "Bluehole","EA Sports"],
                "answer": "Bluehole"
        },
        {
                "question": "What is the maximum number of players can enter into a squad?",
                "option": ["5", "4", "6", "2"],
                "answer": "4"
        },
        {
                "question": "What is the Red Zone?",
                "option": ["Allows you to teleport yourself to any location on the map", 
                        "An area in which bombs randomly drop from the sky", 
                        "An area in which your HP goes back to 100 automatically", 
                        "A safe area in which you can’t be killed"],
                "answer": "An area in which bombs randomly drop from the sky"
        },
        {
                "question": "Do players outside the circular playzone die instantly?",
                "option": ["you are dead right their", 
                        "you gain more health", 
                        "Health decreases gradually, leads to death", 
                        "I never been to the outside of playzone"],
                "answer": "Health decreases gradually, leads to death" 
        },
        {
                "question": "What’s the maximum number of players that can participate in a match?",
                "option": ["100", "50", "150", "90"],
                "answer":"100"
        },
        {
                "question": "Which one of these will heal you back to 100% ?",
                "option": ["Bandages", "Adrenaline Syringe", "Med-kit", "First-Aid Kit"],
                "answer":"First-Aid Kit"
        },
        {
                "question": "Airdrops in the game are made by…?",
                "option": ["A zeppelin", "A helicopter", "An airplane", "A drone"],
                "answer":"An airplane"
        }
        
        
]